translate.ua 2019-06-26

# Privacy Policy

**Trident Software Ltd** (TS, Trident Software) is strongly committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information you provide to effectively and safely process your orders and to provide a more efficient online software activation. We can also use your information to tell you about changes in our services, or about special offers we think you'll find valuable. We provide this service only if you choose to allow us to do so through your account settings. We do not sell, trade or rent your personal information to any other business or outside parties.

**TS** collects and uses your personal information to operate and improve its site and services.

**TS** asks you to provide personal information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address, or telephone number.

We collect additional information about your interaction with **TS** sites and services without identifying you as an individual. For example, we receive certain standard information that your browser sends to every website you visit, such as your IP address, browser type and language, access times and referring Web site addresses. We also use Web site analytics tools on our sites to retrieve information from your browser, including the site you came from, the search engine(s) and the keywords you used to find our site, the pages you view within our site, your browser add-ons, and your browser's width and height.

These uses include providing you with more effective customer service; making the sites or services easier to use by eliminating the need for you to repeatedly enter the same information; performing research and analysis aimed at improving our products, services and technologies; and displaying content and advertising that are customized to your interests and preferences.

If a password is used to help protect your accounts and personal information, it is your responsibility to keep your password confidential. Do not share this information with anyone. If you are sharing a computer with anyone you should always log out before leaving a site or service to protect access to your information from subsequent users.

**TS** is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information we collect on computer systems with limited access, which are located in controlled facilities.
